The Hungry Metal Cardbot
Was there an accident?
Excuse me?
Are you alright?
H-Hello?
Hungry...
Aah!
We received a report that a monster truck transformed into a robot
and ate a battery from an electric car that was passing by on Route 66 last night.
I'm telling you! A gaudy looking truck suddenly started saying it was hungry, and it transformed into a robot...
Mmph? Could this be?
Yes. I'm sure it's a Metal Cardbot.
Jun!
Stop watching TV or you'll be late for school again!
Uh, right!
I'll be off, then!
Do you know where it happened, Jun?
Yes! By the countryside just outside Mowtown-
What was that?
Hahaha, what's got you all jumpy, huh?
Uh... Dad, what are you doing under the car?
Well, the car is acting a little strange.
I think it's broken somewhere. But I just can't figure it out...
Well, I'll be off to school then!
It hasn't been very long, but I had a great time here thanks to all of you.
Thank you, everyone.
Crest!!
I'll never forget the fun times we had!
We're friends for life-
Oh no, Crest!
I can't believe you're leaving us, Crest!
Oh, you mustn't forget me no matter what!
Haha, thank you...
He's been a big star from beginning to end.
You said it!
I hope things will be alright until the farewell party tonight.
The news this morning didn't sound so good.
Everyone's out there looking for the culprit now, so we'll find out soon enough- huh?
Did you find something?
I found traces of oil spilled by a Metal Cardbot.
It might be from the culprit.
Does that mean the culprit was injured?
I can't say for sure.
But it looks like he went downtown.
Okay, I'll leave it to you then.
You can count on me.
What awful timing for the car to break down on the day of the party...
I asked for a rental car, so it should be alright.
Well, I'll be off then!
Take care, honey!
Time to prepare for the party.
Ugh... Don't get it... Just ate...
But me still hungry...
Ah! Oh...
Wha? What the?!
Uh... uh...
When did he bring over the rental car?
Hello? Oh, Edo!
About the car. It seems like the tank is rusty.
It's probably going to take about a week to fix.
What? I'll have to drive around in that gaudy looking truck for a whole week?!
What gaudy looking truck? I haven't sent the rental car over yet.
But what about the one sitting right outside my-?
Huh?
Uh, Edo, I'm sorry. Forget about what I just said. I must have made a mistake.
So, you said the repair would take a week? I'll wait for the rental car then.
Please send a normal car.
-Please send a normal car...
-Me can't... Wait any more! Aagh!
Oh, in an hour? Don't worry, I'll be here. Alright...
No more... WAITING!!
Hello? Hello? Are you still there?
A gaudy looking truck suddenly started saying it was hungry!
Then it transformed into a robot and attacked my car!
Huh... wait a minute!
I found the trail of oil! It's going towards the residential area!
That's where Jun's house is.
Let's hurry!
H-Hey! Hang on!
Wait for us!
Hungry...
Want to... eat that.
You want to eat... the generator?
Gimme!
Then you need to ask nicely!
I said no!
And your hands are all dirty!
Hold still.
There you go.
Now. You have to say "thank you" before eating.
Say, "Thank you for the food".
Thank... you for the food.
Hmph.
Tasty...
Good boy! There you go.
See you tonight, Anna.
Yeah, see you later!
Take care!
Jun.
Blue Cop! Did you find him?
We found that the trail of oil is headed towards your neighborhood.
What?!
Jun! Jun!
Get in. We have a problem at your place!
Wha?! No way!
Huh... what's wrong?
Still hungry.
Huh?
Is there a problem with the voltage?
Hm?
Hold on. Excuse me.
Oh dear. You have a nail in your backside!
This must be the problem.
Stick out your bottom for me.
Like this?
Just like that.
Oh, you poor thing...
Just hang in there.
There, all better!
T-Thank you!
Don't mention it.
But, who are you, anyway?
Me... Buffalo Crush.
I'm Yuri. Finish your meal.
Ok.
He's in our yard?!
Hey, hot pink! What are you doing in my yard?!
Mom?!
Leave my mom alone, right now!
Huh?
Deus Machina's treasure! Metal Breath!
That! Give it here!
So this is why you're taking my mom hostage, huh?!
Hostage? What you mean?
That's enough.
If you're done eating, you should say "thank you for the food!"
Huh?! Thank you for the food.
Jun.
Wild Guardy and I will be at your house soon.
I'm at my house right now. Please hurry.
What? Okay.
Uh... I have something to discuss with you about the repairs.
What? But I have to prepare for the party...
That's Edo's car!
Jun! Are you alright?
Blue Cop! Wild Guardy!
Is that Buffalo Crush? What is he doing here?
Gimme that Metal Breath!
Huh?!
Blue Cop, setup!
Wild Guardy!
He's too strong!
Buffalo Crush full!
Now me unstoppable!
Mega Trucker! Where are you?!
Ugh.
Come on, move it already!
Don't let his strength get the better of you.
Let's overwhelm him with a series of attacks!
Understood!
Wild Guardy, setup!
Come on, then!
That shield puny.
Tomahawk Crush!
Now we got you!
Now! Megabolt Punch!
Megabolt...
Buffalo...
Moonsault!
He's as impenetrable as my shield.
Blue Cop! Let's finish this with Infinity Force Break!
Got it!
Infinity...
Force...
Who's there?!
Is this where you've been roaming about, Buffalo Crush?
That sounds like...
Buster Gallon?
Who is that?!
One of Black Hook's henchmen.
I'm back for the Metal Breath just like I promised, Earthling child.
I never invited you over to my house!
And you're never getting the Metal Breath!
If you want to turn this place into a battlefield, I have no objections!
We leave now.
Excuse me, you want us to what?
Black Hook. You said before.
Real Cardbot always pay back favor.
Our restaurant's sticker?
I suppose if you have your reasons...
A foolish choice. The odds were in our favor.
Set sails to the west. Let's go!
What in the world just happened?
I followed the trail of oil and found an escape pod in the mountains.
Perhaps he was injured during the landing?
And then Jun's mom fixed the oil leak.
So that's what happened.
She must have been surprised!
So it's all thanks to your mother that we were able to have this party.
It's nice but...
Now that there are all these new enemies, I can't help but worry.
I trust that you'll be able to handle them.
I think so too!
We'll be fine as long as we work together!
Promise you'll visit us again, Crest!
Mhm. Of course!